My advice to people around the world is that when a lady comes to you,
telling you... "Man of God I am that having the spirit of this or that" -
please run away!
Congregation: laughing
My God.
Start again!
What I want to tell people around the whole world...be careful
of both married and single women, the are looking for a place to pull you down.
They will be telling you, "Man of God, I am passing through this thing, my belly is aching;
I am having chest pain in the breast."
All this...all that - please run away!
Congregation: laughing
Pastor take your time and say it again. You said that should be careful and what?
Viewers all over the whole world be careful
because this is how I started fooling with young ladies
and married women. They will say, "Man of God I have pain in my waist, touch it!"
Touch it and pray for me.
Man of God, I have pain in my chest, touch it and pray for me.
Man of God, my belly!" Before you know whats going on you are on the other side.
Congregation: laughing
Man of God, touch my chest; I have pain in my chest. Then I would lay my hands.
Then they will say, "Man of God, touch my waist; I have pain in the waist." Then I will lay my hands.
"Man of God touch my tummy." Before you know it, from the tummy you have gone down.
Congregation: laughing
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest: prophecies, deliverances, service, and testimonies.
from the Synagogue Church Of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV. Changing lives, changing nations,and changing the world.